Yes! I'm going to chain Ikimi World whether I'm asleep or awake!
This is Yukirinukoto and Ayumi Kushi!
Comment Patrol~!
Oh, thank you for the applause!
My YouTube comment section
And one more time I said, I'm coming to the comment section of my Instagram.
This is a project to introduce the outrageous comments here!
I was recently featured in Young Jump, so
The comment section is smelly.
I've gathered a lot of comments, so I'd like to introduce them here.
Let's start with the comments on YouTube.
I want to be in your swimsuit for one day!
I don't know about you, but I'd like to be in your swimsuit for one day.
But seriously...
How does it feel to be in a bathing suit for a day?
There's no freedom.
Oh my God, I'm being serious.
And there's this.
Good heavens, Yuki, I found your mole.
Forgive me.
No, but it's okay.
I'm not hiding the mole
This is simple
Maybe no offense
No offense, just a simple swear pattern.
I often tell people not to look at me with pornographic eyes.
But men can't.
If I had to say one thing
You need to get a trainer and work on your hips.
You'll start to see a difference between your left and right buttocks.
I'm serious.
Who the hell are you, really?
This was like a two-step punch.
You can't say that on top of the porn.
If you don't train, you're going to get a left-right difference.
Gross! That's sexual harassment at its finest!Gross! Sexual harassment at its finest!
Damn!
There's a bunch of junior guys outside today.
It just came out of my mouth.
I'm trying to think of swear words for comment patrol, but I can't think of any.
Please don't think for comment patrol!
You can't beat gravity and age, can you, red heart?
You can't just put a heart on anything!
This one is really bad.
I might get a T!
But, Yuriy, you should have a little more meat on you.
You see this a lot, don't you?
I often say that I don't really like it, and then I think, "Well, it's not my favorite opinion.
I thought I could definitely patrol the comments, but there's more to this.
You're so skinny.
I'm worried you're pooping your pants.
I was going in the wrong direction.
I'm so tired.
You know, at first glance, it's like... you know...
You'd think I'd be more of a "you should have more meat on you" type of girl.
It's like...
I've even used letters in a lithoglyphic way.
He even used letters in his lychee.
It's so weird, it's too weird
It's really too weird.
Okay, I'll get to the Insta page in a bit.
Instagram is pretty bad.
But I don't feel bad about it.
What's with all the beautiful lines?
I want to put this up as is.
I'd like to put the text as it is, because the pictograms are funny.
The text isn't so bad, but...
Nice back... you've got a great style.
Thank you for everything, Jan-jan, but...
I've seen it, but the pictograms are so funny. - Do you think he's posting it now?
Do you think he's posting it now?Do you think it's on there now?
It's like this...
Hearts and stuff.
I'm using a lot of love emoticons.
I don't mean to be offensive, and it's not like I'm writing anything weird, but...
I'm just saying that he's probably a prince.
Wait, wait, wait.
Maybe it's the prince. It looks like his picture.
On an iPhone, it's the prince.
It's got to be a swear word at all.
And, well, you know, I've seen this a lot.
I'm going to pretend in my head I'm not wearing them.
Is it transparent? Is it beautiful? Don't be a bean sprout.
He's already started talking shit that has nothing to do with anything.
And one more thing... this uncle... uncle Koubun...
The language is pretty normal.
What a beautiful back shot. It really shows off your style.
But you can see through the tea bag in the bathtub. You're so naughty, Yukirin.
You're too sexy to be an idol.
Wait, that sentence was creepy too.
I'll put it in text too.
So many hearts!
Heart and sweat are never used together.
Remember, Uncle, hearts and sweat are never used together.
There's no next time...
And this one is also very simple...
This one's next.
Eroa-agi yukiyan
I'll say "Eroakiyukiyan".
Eroa giyaki yukiyan
and then "w".
w
I wrote "Eloagiyukyan" from my poodle account.
W
Why is it like that?
I'm worried about yuki, I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you, love you.You're showing too much, Yuki, I'm worried about you, etc. I love you, Shionyan. Love you, love you, love you, love you!
I want to see his face, I don't mean to swear, I just want to hear the image of him.
But you don't swear too much.
I just think it's a little weird.
It's interesting to read comments from overseas.
It's translated.
One said, "Well done!
The other one said it was breathtaking.
Oh, wow.
I mean, maybe it's the translation.
Oh, this sucks.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand it. That's why I said don't do it with his face and full name.
Isn't that bad?
I'm like, "If I upload this screen right now, he's gonna end up like this," you know?
He just took two selfies.
Scary.
But he has 50 followers.
What? Why is that?
Is he a friend?
I'm scared.
Titties, titties, titties.
I didn't even read the song.
Yuki, let's go have tea sometime. Or shaved ice?
I don't think so.
Oh, my God, that's so sexy. I'll take care of it.
I've got it. I've got it. I've got it.
They all have their own faces.
Isn't that amazing? So they don't mean to offend you.
They're probably just...
They're showing their faces and their full names.
What? What?
I translated it into English.
Who is this old woman?
Oh, my God!
She's changed! Don't Japanese people look young to people from overseas?It has changed! Don't Japanese people look young to people from overseas?
Who is this old woman? I've become an old woman!
I'm serious!
I was getting a lot of comments saying "Aphrodite".
Like she's the Aphrodite of this world.
What are you filming? Did you check? Her eyes...
But it's like a Greek goddess or something.
Why is she so famous? I was wondering. I recognized her.
On the last page of Jan-Jan, it definitely says "Aphrodite of this world".
Teyan-chan, you're a little embarrassed by that sentence... "We meet at last..." It's not "here I am..." It looks like I'm talking to you.
Like, "I'm so sorry to keep you waiting." Like, "Gold standing on something is breathtakingly beautiful.
I'm a little embarrassed to do that, too... and that's why I've been seeing so many Aphrodites.
I love it!
I'm sure that if I return to zero now, my face would have been tired in the last few minutes. I'm so tired.
So, I've been patrolling through the comments on Gravure's YouTube videos and Instagram comments,
I've been patrolling through the comments on Gravure's YouTube videos and Instagram comments, and I've noticed that they really don't seem to be trying to hurt her feelings.
But I found it interesting, so I hope to see more of your comments.
I hope you all will comment again.
So, that's all for now, Yukiyuki Kashiwa and Yukiyuki Yukigu. See you again.